dues when paying premiums through mobile
money
under payment reference always indicate
your full name or policy number
payment reference allows input of over
50 characters
a prudential agent paying premiums on
behalf of clients
on the payment reference should always
indicate full name and policy number of
the client
payment reference allows input to over
50 characters
a client using a mobile agent to pay
premiums should ensure that
the mobile agent indicates the client's
full name and telephone number
don'ts when paying premiums through
mobile money
payment references such as below should
not be included
beneficiary name child insured as paya
credential premiums insurance premiums
premiums
agent name the premium
the right way
you